













ROMAN KARPEYEV

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I am a front-end developer and I have experience in creating SPA and dynamic webinterfaces.

I use the following tech stack: React, TypeScript/JavaScript, Redux.

I enjoy what I do and I am focused on personal professional development.

SKILLS

JavaScript (ES5/ES6+), TypeScript, React.js, Redux, HTML, CSS(SASS/SCSS), REST API, Jest, StoryBook, Postman, TDD Material UI, Ant Design Git(GitHub)

EDUCATION

Mechatronics Engineering

Ida-Virumaa Kutsehariduskeskus (2013 - 2017)

• Mechatronics, Robotics, and Automation Engineering

HOW TO REACH ME

<u>karpeyev.com</u>

(L) +372 58 329 597

roman.karpeyev@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

Freelance · Apprenticeship Sep 2021 - Feb 2022 (6 mos)

- · Creating web applications using React, Redux, TypeScript and SCSS (DAL, BLL, UI three-tier architecture).
- · Code refactoring, bug fixing.
- Creating components.
- · Creating Unit Tests.
- Project migration from JavaScript to TypeScript.
- Translating the application from classes to functional components in accordance with the new standards.

Web Developer

Freelance · Apprenticeship Jan 2021 - Aug 2021 (8 mos)

- · Creating website layout interfaces from Figma, Avocode, Photoshop using HTML/SCSS/JS.
- Optimizing web pages for maximum speed and scalability.
- Product functionality testing.
- Active Learning.

COURSES

Individual English lessons

Tarkus OU (May 2022 - in progress)

Front-end course

IT-INCUBATOR (Feb. 2022 - in progress)

JavaScript + React + Redux + TypeScript

- React.js Way of the samurai 1.0, 2.0 (Jun. 2021 ~300 h)
- Udemy courses (Aug 2020 4 mos)